Guide to the Cornell University Medical College, Ithaca Division correspondence,1886-1939.
Cornell University Medical College, Ithaca Division correspondence, 1886-1939
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Medical College, Ithaca Division correspondence, 1886-1939.
19-1-64
Cornell University. Medical College. Ithaca Division.
6.7 cubic ft.
Letters, reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence of Professors Benjamin Freeman Kingsbury, Abram Tucker Kerr, and Simon Henry Gage in their official capacities in the Medical College and the Department of Zoology at Cornell University. Much of the material has to do with the purchase of supplies, admissions to the Medical College (Ithaca Division only), and the granting of fellowships and scholarships. Several of the Annual Reports of the Department to the President are included.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence of Professors Benjamin Freeman Kingsbury, Abram Tucker Kerr, and Simon Henry Gage in their official capacities in the Medical College and the Department of Zoology at Cornell University. Much of the material has to do with the purchase of supplies, admissions to the Medical College (Ithaca Division only), and the granting of fellowships and scholarships. Several of the Annual Reports of the Department to the President are included.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Medical College. Ithaca Division.; Gage, Simon Henry, 1851-1944.; Kerr, Abram Tucker, 1873-1938.; Kingsbury, Benjamin Freeman.; Cornell University. Dept. of Zoology.
Subjects:
Medicine--Study and teaching.; Zoology--Study and teaching.; Medical colleges--Admissions.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence
  - Oct. 1886-July 1908 (Box 1)
  - August 1908-March 1910 (Box 2)
  - April 1910-December 1912 (Box 3)
  - January 1913-December 1915 (Box 4)
  - [Jan.] 1916-[Oct.] 1918 (Box 5)
  - November 1918-July 1920 (Box 6)
  - [Aug.] 1920-[May] 1922 (Box 7)
  - June 1922-April 1923 (Box 8)
  - April 1923-December 1925 (Box 9)
  - January 1926-December 1931 (Box 10)
  - [June] 1932-1938 & undated (Box 11)
  - (1-5-77 add.) (Box 12-14)
- Meeting Minutes and Miscellaneous
  - Minutes of Medical College Faculty, 1898-1938; 2 binders (Box 13)
  - Minutes of Sarah Manning Sage Research funds, 1916-39; 2 binders (Box 13)
  - Sackett Research fund; 1 binder (Box 13)
  - Sage & Sackett funds; 1 binder (Box 13)
  - Mayer Fund; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Minutes of Committee on Doubtful Cases; 1 binder (Box 13)